web-kreation.com 2017-07-04

# Privacy Policy - Web Kreation

**Disclosure and Privacy Policy**

Web Kreation respects your Privacy. We are an interactive information service that connects consumers with information. We are not licensed contractors and are not authorized, nor do we enter into contractual relationships with consumers or individuals that fill out our online forms. While we strive to connect each person that fills out our forms with local experts, it is not possible in all situations. Web Kreation takes your privacy seriously, and we have created this Privacy Statement, to disclose to you our information practices pertaining to the personal information collected about you on our Site. This Privacy Statement applies exclusively to the Site www.web-kreation.com. This statement discloses what information we collect, how we use it, with whom we share it and how we protect it. "Personal Information" refers to information such as Name, or Email, which can be used to identify a person.

**Information Collection and Use**

This Site is an information resource for individuals looking for contractor quotes. A user can utilize our Site without disclosing any personal information. When you select to inquire about a quote, we request your zip code to determine the best quotes in your area.We also collect your name, email address, and phone number to send you the requested quotes. 

We also use your email to send you newsletters when you express your choice to receive them on our Site. This Site may also collect certain information from visitors to, and customers of the Site such as Internet addresses. This Web Site Navigational Information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, to analyze trends, to track users' movements around the Site, and to administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of the Site, and our Service. We may also track and analyze individual usage and volume statistical information ("Aggregated Information") from our visitors and customers.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at corp@web-kreation.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**TCPA**

By submitting, you agree the phone number you provided may be used by Web Kreation and its partners to contact you (including autodialed, pre-recorded calls or text messages). I understand that by consenting I am not required to purchase any products or services.

**Information Sharing**

We may be legally obligated to share your personal information with government agencies, or other third parties under certain circumstances, such as illegal activity on our Site. We reserve the right to disclose your information to our Service Providers, law enforcement, or other government agencies, or in responding to a formal request, such as a judicial proceeding, subpoena, or court order as we, in our sole, and necessary discretion deem appropriate. 

In the event of a sale, merger, or acquisition of some or all of Web Kreation assets, your personal information could likely be a part of the transferred assets. In such an event, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

We may also share aggregated information about users of our Site with third parties.

**Links**

We provide links on our Site to other Web Sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site, and familiarize yourself with these Web Sites' privacy practices, prior to disclosing your personal information to them.

**Access and Opt-Out**

To modify or update the personal information submitted to our Site, please send your request to us using the contact information provided below, and we shall address it. 

In the event that you change your mind about receiving newsletters from our Site, you may unsubscribe from them by selecting the "Unsubscribe" link present in every email we send out.

**Testimonials**

We post customer testimonials on our web site that may contain personal information such as the customer's Name, City, and State. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. Any personal information a user selects to include within their testimonial is not subject to this privacy policy.

**Cookies**

We employ the use of cookies on our Site. A cookie is a small text file set by a web browser, which identifies whether you've visited a site previously. Cookies on our Site contain no personal information. We utilize cookies to provide users' customized content and keep track of the preferences you specify during your use of our Site. Third Party Cookies: We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our Site to help us administer our Site and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual website visitors to any personally identifiable information.

**Clear Gifs (Web beacons/Web Bugs)**

Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Choice and Opt-out."

**Security**

We employ industry-accepted standards in protecting the personal information you provide on our Site. We host the Site in a secure server environment. 

We have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the personal information and Data under our control. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes to this Statement**

We reserve the right to modify this Statement. Should we make a material change to the manner in which we use your collected personal information, we shall notify you by a notice on our Site prior to the changes taking effect. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**

Email: contact@web-kreation.com
